(Amy:)For two people who claim to be
no longer pair-bonded,
(Amy:)you spend an inordinate amount
of time in each other's company.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Amy:)Dare.
(Amy:)I don't believe the rules allow
(Amy:)for an ex post facto
option change.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Okay, look, just because we're
not seeing each other anymore
(Penny:)doesn't mean
we can't be friends.
(Penny:)I mean, Leonard's a great guy.
(Amy:)Then, why did you terminate
your relationship with him?
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Penny:)He got really serious,
and I wasn't ready for it.
(Amy:)Interesting.
(Amy:)How will you react
if, in the future,
(Amy:)you become ready for it,
and Leonard is unavailable,
(Amy:)because another woman
has realized that he is--
(Amy:)to use your words--
"a great guy"?
(Penny:)You can only ask one question.
(Amy and Bernadette together:)That one.
(Bernadette:)You know what,
I don't want to play anymore.